<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Book app with OOP</string>
    <string name="Binavayan_Bio">The book \"Wretches\" written by Malka bin Halil Al-Rowai, the author of \"Orient Mystery\", is a social novel and a family novel that was published in 2012. This book is in the form of a story and depicts the life story of a family.In this book, topics such as love, marriage, family, friendship, life choices and their consequences are examined. The story is in the form of an ongoing narrative and by reading it, you are somehow called into the lives of family members and their relationships.As a social novel, the book \"Les Miserables\" realistically deals with everyday life issues and provides a deep understanding of the relationships between humans and society through characters and events. This book has been able to attract the attention of many readers with its correct and fluent description of the story and its excellent translation.Among the strong elements of the book \"Poor People\", we can mention the attractiveness of the story, the description of the characters of the popular questions of this story, and the fluency and ease of speaking of the author\'s language. By reading this book, you can get to the explanation of the depth of a person, think about and mention correctly topics such as love and wisdom of life, as well as the consequences and results of choices.\n</string>
    <string name="Boy_Book_Bio1">The book delves into themes like the meaning and purpose of life, the bonds and connections between humans, and the pursuit of personal growth and transformation. The author\'s writing style and the beautiful and poignant stories conveyed in the book capture the power and wonder of the narrative, earning it a special place among readers.\n</string>
    The book "Wretches" written by Malka bin Halil Al-Rowai, the author of "Orient Mystery", is a
    social novel and a family novel that was published in 2012. This book is in the form of a story
    and depicts the life story of a family.In this book, topics such as love, marriage, family,
    friendship, life choices and their consequences are examined. The story is in the form of an
    ongoing narrative and by reading it, you are somehow called into the lives of family members and
    their relationships.As a social novel, the book "Les Miserables" realistically deals with
    everyday life issues and provides a deep understanding of the relationships between humans and
    society through characters and events. This book has been able to attract the attention of many
    readers with its correct and fluent description of the story and its excellent translation.Among
    the strong elements of the book "Poor People", we can mention the attractiveness of the story,
    the description of the characters of the popular questions of this story, and the fluency and
    ease of speaking of the author's language. By reading this book, you can get to the explanation
    of the depth of a person, think about and mention correctly topics such as love and wisdom of
    life, as well as the consequences and results of choices.

</resources>